collegedudescash.com 2010-11-21

# P

                        PRIVACY POLICY FOR TIER1CASH,
                                       NETWORK OF WEBSITES
                                    Effective Date: December 8, 2008
                                    Last Modified: December 8, 2008
Tier1Cash.com recognizes that privacy is important. This document discusses the types of personal
information we receive and collect when you use Tier1Cash.com, as well as the actions we take to
safeguard your information.
Personal Information
• Tier1Cash.com collects limited personal information when you become a member or otherwise interact
with us. "Personal information" is information that you provide to us or our business partners which
personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can
be reasonably linked to such information. We will not provide your personal information to third parties
except for billing or other necessary business and legal purposes.
• Tier1Cash.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn
about how you use Tier1Cash.com in order to improve the quality of our services.
• Our servers may automatically record information when you visit our website, including the URL, IP
address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.
Data Uses
• We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that
display customized content and advertising.
• We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve
Tier1Cash.com.
• We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties.
• We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying
with legal process, preventing fraud, or ensuring the security of our infrastructure.
• When you send email or other communication to Tier1Cash.com, we may retain those communications
in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
Your choices
• You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although
some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.
• We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let
you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.
If you have additional questions, please contact us any time at affiliates@tier1cash.com
                                                        1
